在ForecastFragment这个类里  我们去修改
In the Forecast Fragment, we want to modify the
FetchWeatherTask这个类  我们可以
FetchWeatherTask, so that we can pass in the
把邮编这个参数传给它让它执行任务
postal code parameter when we execute that task.
你可以通过快捷键或者点击
You can click on this class, to jump
找到它在哪定义的  然后你就能发现
to where it's defined or you can use this shortcut. And here you see that we
我们修改了它的基础输入类型为 String
modified the generic input type, to be a
在doInBackground()方法里  调用变量params就能得到这个字符串
string so that the doInBackground method receives string params.
现在我们只传入了一个字符串类型的参数
Now, we only passed in one string param,
94043（邮编） 所以在下面
94043. So when you see down here later, we
我们可以通过下标0  获取到数组params的数据
can read out the zeroth position in the params
进而我们就拿到了邮编
array, to get that postal code. Notice that we're
注意我们这里使用了URiBuilder类  把参数一个一个加上去
using the URiBuilder here, and we're appending query
我们为这些参数名预定义了一些常量
parameters, one by one. We define constants for these
看这儿  还有这些值
query params, as seen here. And for the values,
我们都在上面定义过了  你可以想到的是
we also define them up here. You can imagine
未来我们可能会在这个类外面
that in the future these might be configured outside
设定这些变量  现在我们只是把他们放在这里
of this class, but for now we're just going
为确保 URL 是正确的
to define them here. To verify that this URI
我们在这里把这个 URL 输出到
was defined properly, we add a verbose log command
日志调试窗口 我们来一起看看
to print out the built URI. Let's verify that
我们输出的日志信息吧
the log we added actually shows up. In overflow
在右上角菜单栏我们点击刷新（Refresh）  然后
menu we tap Refresh. Then we see the log
我们看到标记着FetchWeatherTask的日志信息打印出来了
tag FetchWeatherTask with our UI printed out. It says
它显示着94043  输出 JSON 格式、公制单位、7天  那么它看起来是正确的咯
94043, jSON format metric units, seven days. So this looks correct.